It's a hotel date today.
今日ホテルデートだね
amazing!
すごい!
Look!
ほら!
copper?
どう?
beautiful!
綺麗!
copper?
どう?
Hotel date.
ホテルデート
Awesome, I'm looking forward to it.
すごい、楽しみ
TRUE?
本当?
I'm kind of looking forward to it.
なんか楽しみ
I can't stand it.
我慢できない
still.
まだ
That's fine.
いいじゃん
still?
まだ?
amazing.
すごい
Not yet.
まだダメ
I have to take off my shoes.
靴脱ぎないと
amazing.
すごい
I can't stand it.
我慢できない
Not yet.
まだダメ
why?
なんで?
cute.
かわいい
I deleted it.
僕消してしまった
I deleted it, right?
僕消してるでしょ
Finish it.
仕上げて
I haven't finished it yet.
まだ仕上げてないけど
good?
いい?
yes.
はい
Finish it.
仕上げて
Go here too.
こっちも行って
Feels good.
気持ちいい
yes.
そう
Go here too.
こっちも行って
Finish it.
仕上げて
Haven't you messed with it?
手出してない?
Broken?
壊れた?
It breaks.
壊れる
Drink.
飲んで
thank you.
ありがとう
It felt good.
気持ちよかった
I can't stand it.
我慢できない
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Here?
ここ か
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
Did you wipe it?
拭いた?
I wiped it though.
拭いたけど
Are you wiping it?
拭いてる?
It's closed.
閉めてる
閉めてるね
It became rusty.
カサカサになっちゃった
First.
先に
I can't stand it.
我慢できない
I'll put it out.
出すから
I'll put it out here.
ここに出すから
Sorry.
ごめんって
it is.
それは
It's been too long.
久々すぎて
I couldn't resist.
我慢できなかった
not good.
良くない
Cunning.
ずるい
Cunning?
ずるい?
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
I wanted to too.
私だってしたかった
TRUE?
本当?
Did you want to?
したかったの?
It's cute.
可愛いね
Hey.
ねえ
Awesome.
すげえ
it hurts.
痛い
Don't hit me.
叩かないで
It's been a while.
久しぶりだ
About 2 months.
2ヶ月くらい
I held back for a long time.
ずっと我慢してた
Have you been holding back?
ずっと我慢してた?
What do you mean?
どういうこと?
I wanted to meet you.
会いたかった
I wanted to.
したかった
Seriously?
まじ?
So cute.
可愛いな
Didn't you do Edge after the last time we were together?
俺と最後した後に エッジはしてない?
I haven't.
してない
TRUE?
本当?
I haven't.
してない
He put up with me.
我慢してくれたんだ
I did it myself.
自分でしてた
Are you going to say that?
それは言うんかい
Tell me clearly.
はっきり言ってね
Because.
だって
Did you do it yourself?
自分でしてたの?
In what way?
どんな風に?
How did you do it?
どんな風にしてたの?
I was doing it.
してた
Do you have any toys?
おもちゃ持ってんの?
I'll buy it for you next time.
今 度買ってあげるよ
Because there are good ones.
いいやつあるから
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみにしてます
I do it when I can't see you.
会えないときはしてます
Have you been holding back for a long time?
ずっと我慢してたの?
Seriously?
まじか
I'm really looking forward to it too.
俺もめっちゃ楽しみなの
It's been a while.
久しぶりだから
This outfit is cute.
可愛いな、この服
Why are you smiling?
なんで笑ってるの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Today, I'm going to edge,
今日さ、 エッジするんだけどさ、
I'm calling a photographer, so please have the photographer take the picture.
カメラマン呼んでるから、 カメラマンの人に撮ってもらって、
I thought I'd do it.
やろうかなと思って
copper?
どう?
Will you be photographed by such a person?
そういう人に 撮られる?
It's nothing but embarrassing.
恥ずかしい以外にない
People can see it.
人に見られるの
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Only two people know.
2人しか知らない
All the time.
ず っとね
It's been a while since I've seen you today, so I asked you to take a picture.
今日は 久しぶりだから 撮ってもらってさ、
Let's have fun.
楽しもう
Peace.
ピースして
You did something just now.
何かしてくれたね、今
What are you going to do?
どうなにするんでしょう?
Well, well, well.
まぁ、 まぁまぁ
Okay, I'm a little concerned.
上、ちょっと気になるね
Show me how it feels.
どんな感じでするのかさ、 見せてよ
Here.
ここね
How does it feel to touch it?
どんな感じでさ、 触る?
touch.
触る
Okay.
いいよ
hand.
手
What always happened?
いつもどうしたよ
Do what you always do.
いつも通りやって
Are you sleeping?
寝てる?
what?
何?
end.
終わり
picture?
え?
end.
終わり
end?
終わり?
what happened?
どうしたの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
let's.
しよう
do?
する?
Shall we do it?
し ようか
I just can't stand it.
ちょっと我慢できない
I can't stand it.
我慢できない
Shall we do it?
しちゃうか?
しちゃう?
It's here.
来た
The camera came.
カメラさん来たわ
Shall we go out?
出よっか
wait a minute.
ちょっと待って
The camera came.
カメラさん来たわ
He came.
来 てくれました
The camera came.
カメラさん来てくれました
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
You look great together.
すごい似合ってるね
That clothes.
その服
Okay, there.
いいよ、そこは
I don't have to upload it.
アップしなくていいんですけどね
I can't see it.
見えない
It's okay, right?
大丈夫でしょ?
It's crispy.
カピカピになってる
It's shiny.
カ ピカピになってる
Well, that is.
まあ、それは
Like, really.
いいね、ほんと
It's been a while
久しぶりだ
hey.
ね
intense.
激 しい
Come out from below.
下から出ちゃって
I'm watching.
見てるよ
Maybe you're watching.
見てるかも
No way.
やだ
what?
な に?
Erotic
エロ
stomach.
い
Genesal Region.
ジ ェネサルリージョン
I don't like it.
嫌だ
what?
なに?
What?
何を?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Look.
ほら
No?
ダメ?
candy?
あめ?
Take care.
気にして
It's getting really warm.
すごい暖かくなってる
why?
なんで?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
It's soaked.
びしょびしょじゃん
No.
ダメ
what?
なに?
I'm doing it.
してる
I started.
始めた
why?
なんで?
Don't hide it.
隠さないで
Would you like me to take a look?
見てもらう?
I don't like it though.
嫌そうだけど
It's so beautiful.
すごい綺麗じゃん
Really?
本当に?
Really.
本当に
No.
ダメ
Hey, Genesar.
ねえ、ジェネサル
I don't like it.
嫌だよ
I hate it.
嫌いだよ
a little bit.
ちょっと
I don't like it.
嫌 だ
嫌だ
hang on.
待って
Japan is high over there.
あそこ日本地高い
Do you know?
知ってる?
I know though.
知ってるけど
Maybe you can watch it from there.
そこから見てるかもね
I can definitely see it.
絶対見える
appear?
見える?
Wait, there's someone over there.
待って、そこに人いる
Look, there are people.
ほら、人がいる
a little bit.
ちょっと
what?
なに?
Isn't it okay to look at this side?
こっち側見ては大丈夫じゃない?
Well, certainly.
まあ、確かに
There are people facing this way.
こっち向いてる人いる
There's a smoking area though.
喫煙所があるけど
I can't see it.
見えてないよ
Anyone there?
いる人?
where are you?
どこにいる?
I'm looking at this side.
こっち側見てる
yes?
そう?
I want to, then.
したいんだよ、じゃあ
How about people?
人どう?
The number of people is increasing.
人増えてる
It's increasing.
増えてる
It's spreading, I guess.
拡散されてるね、なんか
different.
違う
I'm on a different floor.
違う階にいる
It's moving.
動いてるよ
Are you moving it?
動かしてる?
It's not moving.
動かしてない
amazing.
すごい
Amazing, beautiful.
すごい、きれい
Is anyone there?
誰かいる?
Are you watching?
見てる?
Well, let me show you.
じゃあ、見せてあげて
You've gotten better.
上手くなったね
Have you gotten better at blowjobs?
フェラー上手くなった?
Have you always wanted to talk?
ずっと喋りたかったの?
Did you want to talk the day before?
前日喋りたかったの?
Yeah.
うん
Let me take a look.
ちょっと見てもらおうよ
Is there anyone who can see it?
見とる人いる?
There wasn't.
なかった
chance.
チャンス
Look here.
こっち見て
Can I put it in?
入れるの?
Can I come in?
入れていい?
why?
なんで?
No.
ダメ
why?
なんで?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
that's why.
だから
Just a little, just a little.
ちょっとだけ、ちょっとだけ
I'll just do a little bit.
ちょっとだけとかするの
No.
ダメ
No!
ダメ!
What?
何が?
No.
ダメ
Rub it a little.
ちょっとこすって
I'll comfort you.
あやするから
Just rub it.
こするだけじゃ
But you want to, right?
でも、したいでしょ?
Yes, I would like to.
うん、したいけど
Did you forget today too?
今日も忘れちゃった?
I forgot.
忘れちゃった
I'll put it in just because you said it earlier.
さっき言っただけで入れるでしょ
You must have been sleeping a lot.
めっちゃ寝てんじゃん
It's bad, I'm bad too.
やばい、俺もやばい
This is rocky.
これガクガクだね
It feels good, right?
なんか気持ちいいでしょ?
Feels good.
気持ちいい